https://www.sldwebsolutions.com/legal/privacy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This
Statement of Privacy applies to https://www.sldwebsolutions.com and SLD WEB SOLUTIONS and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this
Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to SLD WEB SOLUTIONS include https://www.sldwebsolutions.com and SLDWEBSOLS. The SLDWEBSOLS website is a
Internet Services site. By using the SLDWEBSOLS website, you consent to the
data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your
Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services
offered on our Site, SLDWEBSOLS may collect personally identifiable
information, such as your:
collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to
complete the purchase transaction.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally
identifiable information or personally sensitive data through SLDWEBSOLS's
public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless
you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide
certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or
services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an
account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one
of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties;
(d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other
payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our
Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to,
communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have
requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal
information in the future.
Use of your Personal
Information
SLDWEBSOLS collects and uses your personal information to
operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
SLDWEBSOLS may also use your personally identifiable
information to inform you of other products or services available from SLDWEBSOLS
and its affiliates.
Sharing Information
with Third Parties
SLDWEBSOLS does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists
to third parties.
SLDWEBSOLS may share data with trusted partners to help
perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer
support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from
using your personal information except to provide these services to SLDWEBSOLS,
and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
SLDWEBSOLS may disclose your personal information, without
notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such
action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with
legal process served on SLDWEBSOLS or the site; (b) protect and defend the
rights or property of SLDWEBSOLS; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to
protect the personal safety of users of SLDWEBSOLS, or the public.
Tracking User
Behavior
SLDWEBSOLS may keep track of the websites and pages our
users visit within SLDWEBSOLS, in order to determine what SLDWEBSOLS services
are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and
advertising within SLDWEBSOLS to customers whose behavior indicates that they
are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically
Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be
automatically collected by SLDWEBSOLS. This information can include: your IP
address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website
addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to
maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding
use of the SLDWEBSOLS website.
Use of Cookies
The SLDWEBSOLS website may use "cookies" to help
you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed
on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs
or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and
can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a
convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the
Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you
personalize SLDWEBSOLS pages, or register with SLDWEBSOLS site or services, a
cookie helps SLDWEBSOLS to recall your specific information on subsequent
visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information,
such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to
the same SLDWEBSOLS website, the information you previously provided can be
retrieved, so you can easily use the SLDWEBSOLS features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web
browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser
setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you
may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SLDWEBSOLS
services or websites you visit.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware
that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other
sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read
the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable
information.
Security of your
Personal Information
SLDWEBSOLS secures your personal information from
unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. SLDWEBSOLS uses the following methods
for this purpose:
SSL
Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is
transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption,
such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect
against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network
can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect
your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and
privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and
(b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data
exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Eighteen
SLDWEBSOLS does not knowingly collect personally
identifiable information from children under the age of eighteen. If you are
under the age of eighteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission
to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, SLDWEBSOLS may contact you via email for
the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations,
surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services,
we may receive a notification when you open an email from SLDWEBSOLS or click
on a link therein.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional
communications via email from SLDWEBSOLS, you may opt out of such
communications by replying with UNSUBSCRIBE in the message.
External Data Storage
Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party
hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this
Statement
SLDWEBSOLS reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy
from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we
treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address
specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by
updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site
and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will
constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b)
agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
SLDWEBSOLS welcomes your questions or comments regarding
this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that SLDWEBSOLS has not adhered to
this Statement, please contact SLDWEBSOLS at:
SLD WEB SOLUTIONS
50 Forest St. #1
Keene, NH 03431
Email Us
Telephone number:
